plusgames.com 2012-12-30

# PRIVACY STATEMENT

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**The protection of privacy and the safeguarding of our Clientsג€™ personal information is our highest priority.**

**Please view the following Privacy Statement which clearly explains how we, at PG, collect, process, store and protect your information**

**By opening an account, you hereby give PG your consent to such collection, processing, storage and use of personal information by PG as explained below.**

**The collection of personal information**

PG collects the necessary information required to open your Account and safeguard your privacy and to provide you with the services you desire. To this end, PG gathers information from you which helps us profile your requirements and preferences and provide better services to you.

The information PG collects includes information required to communicate with and identify you. PG may also collect certain demographic information, including, birth date, education, occupation, etc..

**Usage of personal information**

PG uses personal information only as required to provide quality service and security to you. This information helps improve services, customize browsing experience and enables us to inform you of additional products, services or promotions relevant to you and the products and services you require and you consent to us using this data for such purposes.

**Affiliates and Partners**

PG may share information with affiliates in the event such information is reasonably required by such affiliate in order to provide the products or services to you. PG may share information with partners, affiliates and alliances in order to offer additional similar products and services that meet your needs and which are delivered in a manner that is useful and relevant only where you have authorized us to do so. 

**Non-affiliated third parties**

PG does not sell, license, lease or otherwise disclose personal information to third parties, except as described in this Privacy Policy.

PG reserves the right to disclose personal information to third parties where required by law, regulatory, law enforcement or other government authority. PG may also disclose information as reasonably required in order to provide the services to you.

To help us improve our services, PG may engage third parties to help carry out certain internal functions such as account processing, fulfillment, client service, client satisfaction surveys or other data collection activities relevant to our business. Use of the shared information is strictly limited to the performance of the above and is not permitted for any other purpose. All third parties with which PG shares personal information are required to protect such personal information in accordance with all relevant legislation and in a manner similar to the way PG protects the same.

You acknowledge that in order to provide services to you, it may be necessary for information to be transferred outside of the European Economic Area and you consent to such transfer. ****

**Restriction of responsibility**

PG is not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of sites PG links to and has no control of the use or protection of information provided by you or collected by those sites. Whenever You elect to link to a co-branded web site or to a linked web site, You may be asked to provide registration or other information. Please note that such information is recorded by a third party and will be governed by the privacy policy of that third party.

**Use of "COOKIES"**

PG uses cookies to secure your activities and to enhance the performance of the PGג€™s web site. Cookies used by PG do not contain personal information or other sensitive information. 

PG may share web site usage statistics with reputable advertising companies. The information collected by the advertising company is not personally identifiable.

To administer and improve the PG web site, PG may use third parties to track and analyze usage and statistical volume information. The third party may use cookies to track behavior and may set cookies on PGג€™s behalf. These cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information.

**Communications**

Unless otherwise indicated for a particular service, any communications or material of any kind that is e-mailed or otherwise transmitted through the services, including information, data, questions, comments or suggestions will be treated as non-proprietary and non-confidential. 

You grant a license to use such non-proprietary and non-confidential information in any way PG thinks fit, either on the web site or elsewhere, with no liability or obligation to you. PG is free to use any idea, concept, know-how or technique or information contained in such information for any purpose including, but not limited to, developing and marketing products.

**Privacy Statement Updates**

From time to time, PG may update this Privacy Policy. In the event PG materially changes this Privacy Policy including how we collect, process or use your personal information, the revised Privacy Statement will be posted to the web site. You agree to accept posting of a revised Privacy Policy electronically on the web site as actual notice to you. Any dispute over our Privacy Policy is subject to this notice. PG encourages You to periodically check back and review this policy so that You always will know what information PG collects, how PG uses it, and to whom PG may disclose it.
